<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ruby on Rails on Sanketkumar Karve</title>
    <link>http://www.sanketkarve.com/categories/ruby-on-rails/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ruby on Rails on Sanketkumar Karve</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2018 15:56:43 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.sanketkarve.com/categories/ruby-on-rails/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Integrate Vue.js with Rails 5 application</title>
      <link>http://www.sanketkarve.com/blog/vue-rails-integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2018 15:56:43 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.sanketkarve.com/blog/vue-rails-integration/</guid>
      <description>To start with Vue.js and Rails 5 integration let have a quick overview of what we are going to do.
Rails works on Model-View-Controller (MVC) Architecture. Here we will focus on View(V) part of rails. By default, rails support HTML, CSS, and JS but we want to integrate responsive framework to leverage its benefit and make our view more component based. Vue.js will only take care of your view layer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create active admin custom forms in Ruby on Rails</title>
      <link>http://www.sanketkarve.com/blog/active-admin-custom-form-in-ruby-on-rails/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.sanketkarve.com/blog/active-admin-custom-form-in-ruby-on-rails/</guid>
      <description>Active Admin is great gem for administration framework for Ruby on Rails applications.
Here you can find documentation to setup in you Rails applications. Today, Our goal is to create a custom forms in Active Admin. We will create a User and Team model. When a Team is created a user is create along with it and assigned to team. If you are using devise gem and already have existing User model that you can skip the following command to create User model.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lead Shuttle</title>
      <link>http://www.sanketkarve.com/projects/leadshuttle/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.sanketkarve.com/projects/leadshuttle/</guid>
      <description>https://leadshuttle.com April 2018 - Present Lead Shuttle is inbound sales marketing application which is heavily integrated with klenty application. It is customized accouding to sales records with interactive charts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shareito</title>
      <link>http://www.sanketkarve.com/projects/shareito/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.sanketkarve.com/projects/shareito/</guid>
      <description>beta.shareito.com Oct 2017 - Present Shareito help employee to onboarding projects and getting access to resources in less amount of time. Shareito is integrated with many popular applications like G-Suite, GitHub, AWS, Office- 365 and Bitbucket.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Formester</title>
      <link>http://www.sanketkarve.com/projects/formester/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.sanketkarve.com/projects/formester/</guid>
      <description>https://formester.com March 2017 - Oct 2017 (Product Acquired) Formester help user to create customized forms for various purposes like blogging, Mass digital marketing, subscription, invites and much more. Formester provides simple drag and drop tool to create the form and you can just add a script to your code. It provides features like drag and drop, Mail List, Auto Responder, interactive dashboard, Spam Protection and Integrating with various applications like slack, Gmail, and SalesForce.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>